freakify.com 2019-08-06

# Privacy Policy - Freakify.com | Learn Technology : Freakify.com

## Privacy Policy for Freakify.com

At freakify.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by freakify.com and how it is used.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
freakify.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Privacy Policy

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for all pages and services offered by Freakify.com

» Personally Provided Information

You do not have to give us personal information to visit Freakify.com. If you choose to provide us with additional information through an e-mail message, inquiry form, comments, etc., we will only maintain the information as long as needed to respond to your question, inquiry, or to fulfill the stated purpose of the communication. Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, we do not give, share, sell or transfer any personal information to a third party.

» Website Traffic Analysis Software

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, we employ software programs to monitor traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. We also monitor our traffic to analyze visitors’s information, such as, but not limited to, operating system, browsers, screen resolutions and similar.

In the event of authorized law enforcement investigations, and pursuant to any required legal process, information from these sources may be used to help identify an individual.

» E-mail Newsletters

If users wish to subscribe to our e-mail newsletters, we ask for contact information. Our Daily Newsletter is powered by FeedBurner, however we use in-house solution for weekly Newsletter. We/Feedburner use information submitted by you in the same manner as we use contact information described above. Recipients of our newsletters can unsubscribe using the instructions listed at the end of the e-mail newsletter.

SMS Subscription

You are asked to provider certain information if you request to receive daily SMS alerts. We collect this information to keep our SMS broadcast as per the dynamics of our subscribers. Like all other instances, this information will never be given/sold to third party, otherwise asked by the the Law of the Land.

Third Party Advertising Partners

All users of Freakify must keep this in mind that third parties may be placing and reading cookies on your browsers, or using web beacons to collect information as a result of ad serving on Freakify.com.

For, instance one of our partners, Google uses the DoubleClick DART cookie on Freakify.com displaying AdSense for content ads. Similarly, other advertising partners may use their respective cookies to track advertising stats.

» External Links

Our web sites contain links to other sites. Freakify.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each web site to which we may link that may collect personal information. After one year it is our right to remove links from guest posts.

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit[http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

Note: This Page can get updated any time, without an prior noitce, so keep checking back.

Last updated: 22nd March,2013
